autodeal.com.ph 2019-04-26

# Car Buying Simplified in the Philippines | AutoDeal

The following privacy policy applies solely to the AutoDeal.com.ph website located at https://www.autodeal.com.ph and all related websites that redirect to the AutoDeal.com.ph website. 

AutoDeal.com.ph ("we", "us", "our", "the Website") is committed to protect and respect your personal information. This privacy statement explains the personal information we collect, manage, use and disclose in accordance with Republic Act No. 10173, also known as the "Data Privacy Act of 2012". 

It is important that you read this policy to understand the information we may hold about you, how we use it and how you can access or update your information, modify your preferences or request deletion of your personal data. 

## Information Collected 

  1. We may collect a user’s name, telephone number, address and email address at several points throughout the Website. You will need to provide your name and email address in order to receive services from the Website and to establish a point of contact with the businesses registered to our website. 
  2. In order to use the Test Drive function associated with our buyers guide, we will require you to supply your full name, e-mail address and telephone number. This information enables us to pass your details to third parties who will contact you with regards to scheduling a Test Drive. Likewise in order to use the Get Quote function associated with our car guide and promos, we will require you to supply your full name, e-mail address, telephone number and postal address. This information enables us to pass your details to third parties who will contact you with regards to sending you a quotation. 
  3. We collect the IP address of the computer or device which is used to access our Website. 
  4. We employ the use of cookies which are placed by our web servers in order to deliver customized content and better service to our users. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and include expiration dates. You may delete and block all or some cookies from the Website. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all content and services on our Website. 
  5. We employ the use of Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers for purposes of tracking interests, topics and remarketing. We will not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information collected through any Google advertising product or feature without robust prior notice, opt-in and consent of the merger. For users who wish to opt out of their data being used by Google Advertising, we recommend installing the Google Analytics Opt-out browser add-on. (<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>) 

## Use of information

  1. We use the information we collected for the purpose of communicating with our users, such as enabling users to receive e-mail notifications regarding deals they have subscribed to receive alerts about. 
  2. Registered users will also receive email notifications including additional announcements about our products, services and newsletters. We respect the privacy of all of our users and offer an unsubscription service in all of these communications or request removal from the e-mail list by sending an e-mail to [info@autodeal.com.ph](mailto:info@autodeal.com.ph). 
  3. Subject always to applicable law, we may share your information (particularly, names and contact information such as email addresses and phone numbers) with companies that form part of the same group of companies as we do (the “Group Companies”). Such sharing of data shall solely be for the purpose of allowing the Group Companies to offer their services/products to you if, in our opinion, you may be interested in such services and products. In addition, when you register we ask you whether you like to receive offers and services from other third-party companies via email and/or via post. You have the ability to opt-out receiving such third party offers during registration. 
  4. We may also disclose any of your information to any competent governmental authority if asked to disclose such data, without having to notify you. 
  5. Your information will be used and distributed to partner dealers and other third-party partners of the company in accordance with your car buying or selling requests when using the website. Under no circumstance will your information be shared with parties unrelated to your car buying or car selling request. 

## Data Accuracy

In order to keep our records up-to-date, registered users may access their own personal data and make any corrections required to update their information. Users may delete their information from our database by sending an inactive account ticket to [info@autodeal.com.ph](mailto:info@autodeal.com.ph). 

## Data Storage & Security

The security of our users' information is of utmost importance to us. For this reason, the personal information shall be kept through reasonable administrative and security measures to prevent unauthorized access, processing, loss or damage. The personal information are kept in secured servers in which access control and technical measures are implemented. Only authorized employees have the access to the personal information and hold and operate this data under strict confidentiality. 

## Retention

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this policy including the purpose of legal and reporting. The period for which we process and store the personal information may vary depending on the use you make of the Website and the products and/or services we offer. 

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy policy, feel free to contact a customer support representative at [info@autodeal.com.ph](mailto:info@autodeal.com.ph)
